Good morning, rise and shine, everyone!
You're listening to Mariah Radio.
Kai Harada here, keeping you
company on this beautiful morning.
The day is shaping up to be a great one,
and I have just what the doctor ordered.
So sit back, relax, and enjoy.
As you know, I'm a man of loose!
And I never believe in love?
Well, we're back in business.
The reception usually clears
up once you're past the tower.
Anyway, is this your
first time visiting Mario?
Sure is.
Got anything to share?
In terms of recommendations?
Oh, the miso-marinated
beef tongue is real good.
Anything suspicious?
Strange incidents?
Sorry, sir.
But I'm afraid I don't know much when
it comes to oddball stuff like that.
Um, would you kindly remind
me of your destination?
We're going to the front of the station.
Right, almost there.
Good freaking grief.
I swear this better not
be what I think it is.
It happened in April 1999.
It was my first day of high school and I
was about to make two very bizarre friends.
I was about to become a high School and
wondered what the others would be like.
In case you were wondering,
my name's Koichi Hirosei.
Though I guess it's not that important.
Anyway, I was nervously
walking myself to class when...
What?
But didn't I just...
And I thought all my stuff
went flying everywhere.
What the heck's going on?
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention. A giant!
He's got to be over 190 centimeters tall!
Hey, maybe you can help me out.
Here's the thing, I've come here
to find the Higashkata family.
Higashikata?
Let's see.
Maybe an address will jog your memory.
Does Joseonji-16 ring a bell?
Jotaro Kujo.
You can get to Joseonji pretty easily
by taking the number three bus.
It won't be long before
another one comes around.
Thanks, kid.
The first guy that I met was Jotaro Kujo.
Later on, I found out he was 28
years old and a marine explorer.
Apparently,
academics knew him best for his outstanding
research in the field of ecology.
There's this fierceness about him,
but he also seems really intellectual.
Wow.
Hey, you another freshman, little man?
Aren't you gonna introduce yourself?
Right, yes, sir.
I'm Koichi Hirose. Freshman.
Good morning, sir.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, that's more like it, runt.
Man, that was a close one.
You don't have to worry about them.
I'm sure they'll find a different
bus and go about their business.
What do you think you're doing, dickface?
Who do you think you are?
Well, if you really must know,
it seems this little turtle I found
just woke up from hibernation.
But turtles give me the willies.
It takes all my courage to
even touch their shells.
So I thought today would be a good
day to finally conquer my fears.
Buddy, does it look like I give a shit?
Get up, you weirdo.
Well, now, you've got some hype
for such a pathetic freshman.
But here's the deal.
You can dress like a puppet
freak if you want to.
But first you have to pay
your respects to us, got it?
Can you not do that, please?
Reptiles really freak me out.
They're all so creepy.
Just who do you think you're
smirking at, pretty boy?
Forgive me, sir.
I didn't know how things were done.
That's kind of funny,
because I've put a lot
of guys in the hospital
whose last words were
the exact same as yours.
You need to learn some respect, dumbass!
Unless you want to end up
like this stupid turtle!
Man, this guy is heartless.
But hey, I'm feeling merciful.
Leave your jacket and pants with
us, and you get to walk away.
Your cash, too!
Right.
Sorry for the trouble.
A shaman had to go down this way, but
what did he expect in that get-up?
Though it pisses me off,
is that he can just sit back and
watch them pulverize a turtle.
I got an idea, pussy.
Why don't you tell us your name?
Right.
Class 1B.
I'm Josuke Higashikata.
Say what?
Josuke Higashikata?
It says Joe and Joe.
Josuke, huh?
Well, if you ask me, Jojo
has a much better ring to it.
Oh, uh, thanks.
That's very kind of you to say.
Shut your trap and take
off the damn jacket!
Or didn't you notice the bus is here?
If you don't hurry it up, I swear to
God I'll chop off that fogly cowlick!
Did you hear what I said?
Hurry it up!
Sure, but first...
Question.
Could you repeat what you
just said about my hair, sir?
A stand?
My nose! My teeth!
Talk shit about my hair and
you'll see a different side of me.
A side that'll make you
feel pain like never before.
So what was that about my hair
looking like a motley toupee?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
No one said!
I know what I heard,
dammit! What happened?
That pump went flying through the air!
There's no denying what I just saw.
That was a stand.
What?
It's like the turtle's
cuts were never there.
What the hell's going on?
Your nose and teeth
are healing themselves!
Look at that! He's fixed!
Yeah, I guess, but why
is his face all weird?
It looks totally different now.
What is it?
What happened to my face?
Well, what?
You've really done it now.
You made me touch something that
I didn't want to lay a finger on.
So how exactly do you plan
on making it up to me, huh?
Wait, come back here!
You can't leave!
What happened to my nose? Guys, wait!
They were a hassle.
And this guy...
Holy shit!
Oh, it's just that turtle again.
So I was right.
Somehow, the turtle's completely healed.
Josuke Higashkata.
You were born in the year 1983.
Mother's name, Tomoko.
She was 21, attending university in Tokyo.
This town's the only
home you've ever known.
But everything changed in 1987, when you
came down with a mysterious fever at age 4.
For 50 days, you were a
knock away from death's door.
Your father's name is...
Good grief.
How'd I get mixed up in this?
The name of your father is Joseph Joestar.
He's 78 now, and the
founder of Joestar Realty.
The Joseph Joestar?
He's that American real estate mogul.
Don't worry, the old man's fine.
But one day I was looking into
how to divide his properties.
That's when I discovered you, his
son, living right here in Japan.
Even the old man had no idea.
Piece of shit that he is.
The bastard always said his
wife was his one and only.
Then I find out he had an affair
at the ripe old age of 62.
And the product of it is you.
Sorry, guess I shouldn't have said that.
My name is Jotaro Kujo.
Which means, since he's my grandfather,
I'm technically your nephew. Bizarre, huh?
Nephew?
Huh? Pleasure.
We can talk on the way.
So, there you have it. Eventually,
you're going to find yourself in possession
of a third of the old man's inheritance.
That's the message I
came here to tell you.
I hate to lay this on you,
but this affair has turned the
Joestar family upside down.
Er, upside down? Are you
serious? I am. My grandma,
Susie Q, is the angriest she's
ever been in their entire marriage,
and they've been together 61 years.
What?
Please forgive me!
This is all my fault!
Hey, there's no need to freak out.
Why are you apologizing
in the first place?
Well, I...
I'd hate to be the cause of
the family falling apart.
Whenever the subject came up, Mom
told me she was deeply in love.
Knowing that she had
that is enough for me.
Could you tell my dad?
I mean, Mr. Joestar.
He doesn't need to concern
himself with us. Thank you.
What's with this kid?
I came here ready to be decked
on behalf of the old man.
But instead of being angry,
he's the one apologizing to me.
Look, it's Josuke! Yeah, it is!
Hey, Josuke! What a coincidence!
Let's go to class together!
Your hair is looking glorious as ever!
It's so great!
You're so different from
the other guys at school!
That's great, but we're actually in
the middle of an important chat, so...
Aw, come on!
If you don't hurry, you're
gonna be late for school!
We can talk later!
Earth to Josuke.
We haven't finished our business yet.
Get the groupies out of here.
Who the hell's this guy?
Hey, you can cackle like hens
about his hair on your own time.
This guy has no idea the
beast he's just released.
Why'd he talk about his hair that way?
Bastard.
Do you want to repeat what
you just said about my hair?
Oh, this isn't good.
You don't have to tell me.
The one thing that sets Josuke off like
nothing else is someone insulting his hair.
This is just what happened before.
Hold on a minute, Josuke.
I wasn't trying to take
a shot at your hair.
Damn, here he comes!
Josuke, no! He's bleeding!
Do you see it, Josuke?
This is called a stand.
It's a physical manifestation of the soul.
Joseph has one of these as well.
Only a stand user can see another stand.
You know, it pisses me off when someone
decides to badmouth my pride and joy.
It really grinds my gears!
So that's what his stand looks like.
This kid's power is unreal.
Don't know if you realize this, nephew,
but you left your chest wide open!
Enough!
Where did he...?
How'd that happen?
What the heck is going on?
Why, Hugh?
When did...?
Josuke!
Shut your mouths and
get the hell out of here
before your whiny
bitching makes me angrier.
Okay.
They must know each other.
He's kind of scary.
Yeah, but in a hot way.
Unreal.
I don't understand.
What just happened?
I can't wrap my head around any of it.
It's been a while.
Ten years to be exact.
I only managed to stop
time for half a second.
I doubt we would have killed
each other if I hadn't,
but it would have gotten
ugly for one of us.
Here, I got you.
No, it's okay.
I can manage on my own.
Fair enough.
As I was saying, there's another
reason I came to see you.
Look at this picture.
Do you see it?
Something evil is lurking in this town.
A catastrophic danger is
closing in as we speak.
When the old man used his psychic
photography to get a picture of you,
this was the result.
We don't know who this guy is, but if I
had to guess, I'd say he's a stand user.
I know this is all new to you, but
I wanted to show you the picture.
Don't let your guard down.
Koichi, if you ever run into
him, get as far away as you can.
Getting the police involved won't help.
Just haul ass.
Josuke,
if you find yourself face to face with
him, keep your cool and stay out of it.
Or it'll be a repeat
of what happened here.
Our orientation!
You're right!
It started!
My mom is gonna kill me if I show
up late for my first day of school!
Hey, I need to get going,
but I promise to listen to whatever
you have to say after school, okay?
You're Koichi, right?
Come on, let's take off!
Huh?
Put some pep in your step!
Right!
This is Josuke Higashikata.
He's one of the other bizarre
friends I made that year.
One second he's a wallflower, the
next he's acting like a crazy person.
He's got some family drama going on.
That's one way to make a first impression.
Chosuke.
That kid's a strange one.
Not to mention his stand.
Given that my hat isn't
currently ripped all hell,
it must be able to destroy objects
and rearrange their structure.
If he'd managed to connect
with my face or my skull,
I don't even want to think about it.
But he could be a potential ally.
He's already a more than capable fighter.
Excluding his fickle personality, that is.
Regardless, I'm really hoping this mess
doesn't have anything to do with Josuke.
Hey, good looking!
Where you headed?
I'll take you where you want.
There's no need to be shy, honey.
I don't bite much.
Come on, get in.
Damn, lady, you're a total knockout.
So you're saying you'll
go wherever I want, huh?
You had better believe it.
Just say the word and I'm there.
In that case, why don't you take
a one-way trip to hell, douchebag?
What the hell?
Hey there, son.
You all right?
Help me, officer!
You got here just in time
to catch that crazy bitch!
She assaulted me! Sorry, son.
Hate to say it, but you're on your own.
What?
That woman is my daughter. Huh?
And in addition to
being a public nuisance,
you also referred to my
baby girl as a crazy bitch,
so I'd watch myself if I were you.
I'll let you off with a warning,
but you're on thin ice, got it.
Oh, dear, Madame Murakami,
how are you holding up?
I'll carry this so you can take it easy.
Huh?
Fancy seeing you here, Tomoko. Hey, Dad.
On your way home? Sure am.
I'll keep you company.
I'm all done with my shift for the day.
How's Josuke doing?
Today's his orientation.
That boy had better not
be getting into trouble.
Right.
Who knows with that kid?
He looks innocent, but the moron
loses it at the drop of a hat.
I wonder where he gets that from.
All right, settle down.
But... Huh?
Deep in his heart of hearts, he's
an honest-to-goodness sweetie pie.
I'm not too worried about it.
That's the spirit.
How do you feel about having
a big celebration tonight?
Sounds good.
That was actually my plan.
I doubt he'll come straight home, though.
That child of mine likes his detours.
That he does.
Hey, I want to stop by Kameyu, can we?
Are you crazy?
I just bought you an
expensive bag, remember?
Please, baby, I want to
look at clothes today.
Watch it, dumbass!
Pay attention to where
you're walking, fool.
That freak show gave me the creeps.
What kind of moron slams into
someone and doesn't apologize?
Forget him.
Let's just get out of here, babe.
Yeah, yeah, you're still
angling for Kameyu, aren't you?
Angelo Katagiri, a .k .a. Angelo.
He was born in Morioh in
1964 and has an IQ of 160.
He was sent to Juvie for robbery and
rape when he was only 12 years old.
That was the beginning of his depravity.
He earned a reputation for
being the most violent,
abominable criminal to
ever walk on Japanese soil.
Most of his youth was spent in jail.
By the time he turned 34, he'd
already spent 20 years in the
slammer.
The final crime he ever committed was so
reprehensible, he'd make a sewer rat puke.
He was eventually arrested,
and then executed.
But unfortunately for all
involved, the execution
didn't stick.
Angelo escaped from custody shortly after,
and he most likely became a Stand user
right before his execution I'm not sure
why but he's now hiding in the shadows
of this quiet town and I have no idea
where oh hey Koichi
you headed home uh
yeah guess so so we're classmates yeah
what a coincidence well I'll catch you
tomorrow have a good evening hey uh Josuke,
can you wait a moment?
Huh?
I see.
You want to hear what that
Jotaro guy has to say, don't you?
I can't get it out of my mind.
It's happening in our backyard.
Admirable of you to care.
But I'll pass. But why?
Not gonna lie, I was curious
about the whole thing at first.
But when I thought about it,
I figured it'd be best to keep clear
of this whole love-child fiasco.
Huh? How come?
Well, things are fine the way they are,
so in my opinion, why try
to fix what ain't broke?
Yeah, I get it.
What's going on?
Maybe it's some kind of accident.
You want to go and check it out?
Mm-hmm.
This area's not safe.
You need to get back right now.
It's absolute chaos over here.
Some man went to rob
that convenience store
and he's taken the
female employee hostage!
Look! He's coming out!
Freeze!
Put down the knife!
Just let the girl go!
Shut up and get the hell back, all of you!
Hey, I recognize that lady.
She's been my cashier a couple of times.
Judging by his eyes, if he actually snaps,
he'll kill her without any hesitation.
Last chance!
Get out of my way!
I'm taking the car and
leaving this isn't good.
We have to get out of here
before things get worse.
Yeah, you're probably you over
there with a dumb shit hairdo
I told your ass to get away from the car.
What do you want me to kill you?
I have a bad feeling
This is gonna get ugly.
Yep, I knew it!
Oh no, here it comes?
Why in the world did it have to happen
right here right now especially after mr.
Your joltaro warned him!
Who the devil is that?
Stand down and back away!
What the hell did you
just say about my hair?
I don't know who you think you are,
but if you don't start walking,
I'm gonna gun her like a fish!
Get back in here!
If that guy snaps, you're a dead man!
That goes for you too, now get away!
I've had all I'm gonna take!
You're all driving me crazy!
I'm gonna freakin' do it!
I'm gonna slaughter this bitch!
Oh, is that a fact?
Yorah!
What the?
Those two have a hole
through their bodies!
I didn't piss you off, did I?
Because I should be the
one who's ticked off.
But how?
There's not a mark on me.
She's back to normal, like before.
My knife's inside my body!
How did my knife get inside?
Hey!
What did you do?
I suggest finding a surgeon to
remove that in the prison hospital.
Quickly, let's cuff this guy!
What's going on around here? Josuke!
What's up, Koichi? Are you okay?
That was...
What the hell is happening?
Well, what a surprise!
It appears another annoying
stand user has joined the fray!
And I was having so much fun using
that meat puppet for my armed robbery.
But of course, you had to
get in my way. Hang on.
He's from the picture, huh?
So you know I'm going to
keep a close eye on you.
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
I'll be nearby watching and waiting.
What did you say, water boy?
Josuke!
What the hell were you thinking?
You could've been killed!
Wait a minute!
Mr.
Jotaro was telling the truth all along.
Something's happening in this town.
It's almost as if I
can feel it in the air.
Whatever found its way
into Mariah... It's...
it's monstrous.
Hey, Josuke, can you get the phone?
What are you doing, Josuke?
Answer the damn phone!
Yeah, yeah, don't have
a cow, I'm getting it.
Hello?
It's Jotsuro.
Oh, hi.
Our conversation yesterday was too brief.
We need to talk about the
guy hiding in this town.
Um, I wanted to talk about that too.
We should meet.
You staying somewhere in town?
I'm at the Mariah Grand Hotel for now.
What's on your mind?
Well, to be honest.
Damn it, this really pisses me off.
Where the hell did I put that damn shovel?
What a little brat.
He's living the high life with
his perfect little family.
He's even got a hot young mom.
Not that he could appreciate it.
That kid's such a lucky bastard.
Josuke Higashkata.
You'd better not get too
cocky, you little pissant.
Because I'm going to stomp your
soul and your precious little life.
I'm going to get to have my fun after all.